Who else found themselves in India?
The East India Company?
Those guys stuck around for a while, huh?
Do you know the first thing they traded with India was?
Cinnamon.
That's what led to 200 years of oppression.
The one spice we use least in Indian cooking.
Tell me you did this for garam masala and I understand.
Fuck, you want bhindi, you can attack us again.
I get it.
I mean, cinnamon?
You ever been at a dining table,
somebody's like,
you have more cimmanon for the tikka?
Fuck off.
Cinnamon.
That's like me colonizing England for sunlight, man.
Are you insane?
Cinnamon.
But the bright side is because we gave you cinnamon,
we get to feel part of your process.
You know what I mean?
At least now you know that Muslims and Hindus
gave you that Christmas spirit.
Cinnamon.
Yeah, that came from us, guys.
Those things Santa Claus was whipping,
they were brown, but they weren't reindeer.