But yes, everybody can be rich.
And let me give you a thought exercise.
Imagine if tomorrow we could wave a wand
and everybody was trained
as a scientist or an engineer.
Everybody.
Even if you weren't very good.
You had enough understanding of computers,
you could write some code,
you could build some hardware.
And don't tell me people can't do it.
Because they can.
That's just the tyranny of soft expectations.
That's just you looking down on somebody else.
They can't do it.
They just have to be educated.
But they're educated all as hardware, software, engineers,
scientists, biologists, technicians.
Hard sciences, not the social sciences.
We would all be done within five years.
Robots would be doing everything
from cleaning toilets to cooking food
to flying airplanes to driving Ubers.
And what would we be doing?
We would be doing all creative jobs
to entertain each other
and researching science and technology.
We would have wonderful lives.
So it is really just a question of education.