Hello friends, Indians by nature are innovative and creative and recognizing this streak, the
government of India adopted the national intellectual property rights property policy
last year. Ever since, we have come through with a lot of programs for our young innovators
or creators for the entrepreneurs of India, so that they can utilize their IP, their intellectual
property and benefit from it gain economic benefits out of it. At the same time, we are
also conscious that for the creators and innovators to be able to enforce their IPRs, the intellectual
property rights, the enforcement and adjudication mechanisms in the country have to be strengthened,
have to be sensitized. In this regard, we are organizing a national IPR enforcement workshop,
which is going to be inaugurated by the honorable homelessness of India on the 22nd of August.
We hope to sensitize police officers across the country and create a kind of movement where
people are able to enforce their IPRs, are able to enjoy the benefits of their IPRs without fear and
with having the full rule of law behind them. At the same time, we are also acutely aware of the
need to create awareness on IPRs in school children and college students in the general public,
in the industry, so that they can recognize their own IPRs, protect their IPs as also respect other
IP. And this awareness program has already started, we have launched at a number of schools,
colleges and industry, industrial clusters. In the days to come and in the months to come,
we certainly hope to see the IP landscape of India changing and changing for the better.
Thank you.